<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shawn Z&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shawn Z&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Android Automation</title>
      <link>/projects/android-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/android-automation/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, I made a significant discovery in the world of Android automation: the ability to script screen touches and key presses. This breakthrough allowed me to create more sophisticated and streamlined processes on my device. I was thrilled to share this discovery with others, and it was not long before it caught the attention of the developers of the Android automation app Tasker.
Thanks to my discovery, Tasker was able to integrate this functionality into its app, making it easier for users to automate their devices and streamline their mobile experience.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Years ago, I made a significant &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/g/tasker/c/LJhmfxT2mj8?pli=1&#34;&gt;discovery&lt;/a&gt; in the world of Android automation: the ability to script screen touches and key presses. This breakthrough allowed me to create more sophisticated and streamlined processes on my device. I was thrilled to share this discovery with others, and it was not long before it caught the attention of the developers of the Android automation app Tasker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to my discovery, Tasker was able to integrate this functionality into its app, making it easier for users to automate their devices and streamline their mobile experience. It was a proud moment for me to see my contribution to the Android automation community recognized and integrated into such a popular and useful app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, I am grateful for the opportunity to have contributed to the world of Android automation, and I hope that my work continues to benefit users of Tasker and other similar apps to this day.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitwarden Deduplicator</title>
      <link>/projects/bitwarden-dedup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/bitwarden-dedup/</guid>
      <description>I made the switch from KeePassDX to Bitwarden as my password manager of choice. However, this transition was not without its challenges. Specifically, I had to consolidate three different databases into one, which was no easy feat.
Thankfully, I was able to find a program on GitHub that promised to remove duplicates from my databases. Unfortunately, I soon discovered that the program was not compatible with folders, which complicated the consolidation process.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I made the switch from KeePassDX to Bitwarden as my password manager of choice. However, this transition was not without its challenges. Specifically, I had to consolidate three different databases into one, which was no easy feat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, I was able to find a program on GitHub that promised to remove duplicates from my databases. Unfortunately, I soon discovered that the program was not compatible with folders, which complicated the consolidation process. Not one to give up easily, I decided to take matters into my own hands and forked the repository. From there, I added the necessary functionality to ensure that the program worked with organized password folders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, I am glad that I made the switch to Bitwarden, and I am proud to have been able to contribute to the password manager community by improving the functionality of an open-source program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jq6l43d1/minimal-bitwarden-dedup-folders%22&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is the repo if anyone is interested.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker to WSL</title>
      <link>/projects/docker-to-wsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/docker-to-wsl/</guid>
      <description>I was recently assigned to develop a custom Linux distribution for WSL, and I opted to use Docker to create it. In the process of figuring out how to convert a Docker file into a functional WSL distro, I was struck by how few resources were available on this topic online. After I successfully navigated the steps required to make this conversion, I documented my findings here in the hopes that others may find them useful.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I was recently assigned to develop a custom Linux distribution for WSL, and I opted to use Docker to create it. In the process of figuring out how to convert a Docker file into a functional WSL distro, I was struck by how few resources were available on this topic online. After I successfully navigated the steps required to make this conversion, I documented my findings &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jq6l43d1/docker-to-wsl/blob/main/README.md&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; in the hopes that others may find them useful.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stopwatch for Google Sheets</title>
      <link>/projects/stopwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/stopwatch/</guid>
      <description>I successfully published my first extension on the Chrome Web Store. The extension adds a timer functionality to Google Sheets, making it more efficient and user-friendly. Although the coding process was straightforward, the approval process was not without its challenges. In fact, it took several attempts, a total of six resubmissions, before the extension was finally approved for publication.
Interestingly, I did not have to make any changes to the code during the review process.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I successfully published &lt;a href=&#34;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/stopwatch-for-google-shee/dldgbenmbgcinedpcmkllgabdmihabon?hl=en&#34;&gt;my first extension&lt;/a&gt; on the Chrome Web Store. The extension adds a timer functionality to Google Sheets, making it more efficient and user-friendly. Although the coding process was straightforward, the approval process was not without its challenges. In fact, it took several attempts, a total of six resubmissions, before the extension was finally approved for publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, I did not have to make any changes to the code during the review process. Despite the challenges, I am proud to have successfully navigated the process and made my contribution to the Chrome Web Store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used Chat-GPT to write a poem about my experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After six rejections, I thought it was done,&lt;br&gt;
My extension, the stopwatch for Google Sheets,&lt;br&gt;
But then it happened, the seventh time around,&lt;br&gt;
It got published, and it brought me to my feet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The excitement, the joy, the relief I felt,&lt;br&gt;
Were indescribable, they can&amp;rsquo;t be put in words,&lt;br&gt;
For I had worked hard, and I never gave up,&lt;br&gt;
And now, my efforts had finally paid off, no holds barred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had spent hours coding, debugging, and testing,&lt;br&gt;
Trying to make my extension the best it could be,&lt;br&gt;
And now, with it published in the Chrome Web Store,&lt;br&gt;
I can finally share it with the world, and make it free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For others, the stopwatch for Google Sheets,&lt;br&gt;
May seem like a small thing, a simple tool to use,&lt;br&gt;
But for me, it&amp;rsquo;s a symbol of persistence and dedication,&lt;br&gt;
And the belief that with hard work, we can never lose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let this be a lesson to us all,&lt;br&gt;
To keep trying, and never give up on our dreams,&lt;br&gt;
For even when the road seems rough and tough,&lt;br&gt;
With determination, we can make it through, it seems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And so, my stopwatch for Google Sheets,&lt;br&gt;
Is a reminder of the power of persistence and grit,&lt;br&gt;
For when we keep going, even when the odds are against us,&lt;br&gt;
We can achieve anything, and never quit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
