<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shawn Z&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shawn Z&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/posts/shawn-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shawn-z/</guid>
      <description>I am a tech enthusiast and my passion lies in exploring the endless possibilities that technology has to offer. I am a Linux devotee, and I am always eager to learn and experiment with new tools and techniques. My expertise lies in programming, and I am skilled in various programming languages such as Python, Go, Bash, and Javascript.
When I am not working on tech-related projects, I enjoy indulging in my hobbies.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I am a tech enthusiast and my passion lies in exploring the endless possibilities that technology has to offer. I am a Linux devotee, and I am always eager to learn and experiment with new tools and techniques. My expertise lies in programming, and I am skilled in various programming languages such as Python, Go, Bash, and Javascript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I am not working on tech-related projects, I enjoy indulging in my hobbies. I have been juggling for several years now, and I find it to be a great way to unwind and clear my mind. I am also an avid chess player, and I particularly enjoy playing the game&amp;rsquo;s exciting variant, Crazyhouse. In my free time, I love to read books on a variety of topics, including psychology, chemistry and fiction. Additionally, I have a keen interest in the Japanese language and culture, and I am always studying new things to expand my knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I created this website to share my experiences and knowledge with others who share my passion for technology and the things I enjoy. Through this platform, I hope to connect with like-minded individuals, share my thoughts and insights, and learn from others. Whether you are a fellow tech enthusiast, a juggling aficionado, or simply someone looking to learn something new, I hope you find something valuable here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for visiting my website, and feel free to reach out if you have any questions or would like to connect.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Automation</title>
      <link>/projects/android-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/android-automation/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, I made a significant discovery in the world of Android automation: the ability to script screen touches and key presses. This breakthrough allowed me to create more sophisticated and streamlined processes on my device. I was thrilled to share this discovery with others, and it was not long before it caught the attention of the developers of the Android automation app Tasker.
Thanks to my discovery, Tasker was able to integrate this functionality into its app, making it easier for users to automate their devices and streamline their mobile experience.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Years ago, I made a significant &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/g/tasker/c/LJhmfxT2mj8?pli=1&#34;&gt;discovery&lt;/a&gt; in the world of Android automation: the ability to script screen touches and key presses. This breakthrough allowed me to create more sophisticated and streamlined processes on my device. I was thrilled to share this discovery with others, and it was not long before it caught the attention of the developers of the Android automation app Tasker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to my discovery, Tasker was able to integrate this functionality into its app, making it easier for users to automate their devices and streamline their mobile experience. It was a proud moment for me to see my contribution to the Android automation community recognized and integrated into such a popular and useful app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, I am grateful for the opportunity to have contributed to the world of Android automation, and I hope that my work continues to benefit users of Tasker and other similar apps to this day.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitwarden Deduplicator</title>
      <link>/projects/bitwarden-dedup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/bitwarden-dedup/</guid>
      <description>I recently made the switch from KeePassDX to Bitwarden as my password manager of choice. However, this transition was not without its challenges. Specifically, I had to consolidate three different databases into one, which was no easy feat.
Thankfully, I was able to find a program on GitHub that promised to remove duplicates from my databases. Unfortunately, I soon discovered that the program was not compatible with folders, which complicated the consolidation process.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I recently made the switch from KeePassDX to Bitwarden as my password manager of choice. However, this transition was not without its challenges. Specifically, I had to consolidate three different databases into one, which was no easy feat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, I was able to find a program on GitHub that promised to remove duplicates from my databases. Unfortunately, I soon discovered that the program was not compatible with folders, which complicated the consolidation process. Not one to give up easily, I decided to take matters into my own hands and forked the repository. From there, I added the necessary functionality to ensure that the program worked with organized password folders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, I am glad that I made the switch to Bitwarden, and I am proud to have been able to contribute to the password manager community by improving the functionality of an open-source program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jq6l43d1/minimal-bitwarden-dedup-folders%22&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is the repo if anyone is interested.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>/contact/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please feel free to contact me via email at s.shawn.zimmerman@gmail.com.
I look forward to hearing from you and will do my best to respond in a timely manner.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to contact me via email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:s.shawn.zimmerman@gmail.com&#34;&gt;s.shawn.zimmerman@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to hearing from you and will do my best to respond in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker to WSL</title>
      <link>/projects/docker-to-wsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/docker-to-wsl/</guid>
      <description>I was recently assigned to develop a custom Linux distribution for WSL, and I opted to use Docker to create it. In the process of figuring out how to convert a Docker file into a functional WSL distro, I was struck by how few resources were available on this topic online. After I successfully navigated the steps required to make this conversion, I documented my findings here in the hopes that others may find them useful.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I was recently assigned to develop a custom Linux distribution for WSL, and I opted to use Docker to create it. In the process of figuring out how to convert a Docker file into a functional WSL distro, I was struck by how few resources were available on this topic online. After I successfully navigated the steps required to make this conversion, I documented my findings &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jq6l43d1/docker-to-wsl/blob/main/README.md&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; in the hopes that others may find them useful.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juggling</title>
      <link>/videos/juggling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/videos/juggling/</guid>
      <description>I created a video showcasing my juggling skills for my company&amp;rsquo;s talent show.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I created a video showcasing my juggling skills for my company&amp;rsquo;s talent show.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1fur9XrCa2ezdtWgSkIHqN0ee_ARrKdyv/preview&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; allow=&#34;autoplay&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stopwatch for Google Sheets</title>
      <link>/projects/stopwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/stopwatch/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I successfully published my first extension on the Chrome Web Store. The extension adds a timer functionality to Google Sheets, making it more efficient and user-friendly. Although the coding process was straightforward, the approval process was not without its challenges. In fact, it took several attempts, a total of six resubmissions, before the extension was finally approved for publication.
Interestingly, I did not have to make any changes to the code during the review process.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I successfully published &lt;a href=&#34;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/stopwatch-for-google-shee/dldgbenmbgcinedpcmkllgabdmihabon?hl=en&#34;&gt;my first extension&lt;/a&gt; on the Chrome Web Store. The extension adds a timer functionality to Google Sheets, making it more efficient and user-friendly. Although the coding process was straightforward, the approval process was not without its challenges. In fact, it took several attempts, a total of six resubmissions, before the extension was finally approved for publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, I did not have to make any changes to the code during the review process. Despite the challenges, I am proud to have successfully navigated the process and made my contribution to the Chrome Web Store.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
